 export const games =  [
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20company%20developed%20the%20video%20game%20%22Borderlands%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Gearbox%20Software",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2K%20Games",
"Activision",
"Rockstar%20Games"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20city%20of%20Rockport%20is%20featured%20in%20which%20of%20the%20following%20video%20games%3F",
"correct_answer": "Need%20for%20Speed%3A%20Most%20Wanted%20%282005%29",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Infamous%202",
"Saints%20Row%3A%20The%20Third",
"Burnout%20Revenge"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Portal%202%2C%20the%20iconic%20character%20GLaDOS%20is%20turned%20into%3A",
"correct_answer": "A%20potato",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20tomato",
"A%20lemon",
"An%20apple"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Excluding%20their%20instructor%2C%20how%20many%20members%20of%20Class%20VII%20are%20there%20in%20the%20game%20%22Legend%20of%20Heroes%3A%20Trails%20of%20Cold%20Steel%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "9",
"incorrect_answers": [
"6",
"10",
"3"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20which%20order%20do%20you%20need%20to%20hit%20some%20Deku%20Scrubs%20to%20open%20the%20first%20boss%20door%20in%20%22Ocarina%20of%20Time%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "2%2C%203%2C%201",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1%2C%202%2C%203",
"1%2C%203%2C%202",
"2%2C%201%2C%203"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20game%20series%20%22The%20Legend%20of%20Zelda%22%2C%20what%20was%20the%20first%203D%20game%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ocarina%20of%20Time",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Majora%27s%20Mask",
"A%20Link%20to%20the%20Past",
"The%20Wind%20Waker"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20Kingdom%20Heart%20series%20who%20provides%20the%20english%20voice%20for%20Master%20Eraqus%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mark%20Hamill",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jason%20Dohring",
"Jesse%20McCartney",
"Haley%20Joel%20Osment"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "When%20was%20%22Garry%27s%20Mod%22%20released%3F",
"correct_answer": "December%2024%2C%202004",
"incorrect_answers": [
"November%2013%2C%202004",
"December%2013%2C%202004",
"November%2012%2C%202004"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "%22Rollercoaster%20Tycoon%22%20was%20programmed%20mostly%20entirely%20in...",
"correct_answer": "x86%20Assembly",
"incorrect_answers": [
"C%2B%2B",
"C",
"ALGOL"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20game%20%22Cave%20Story%2C%22%20what%20is%20the%20character%20Balrog%27s%20catchphrase%3F",
"correct_answer": "Huzzah%21",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Yes%21",
"Whoa%20there%21",
"Nyeh%20heh%20heh%21"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20protagonist%20of%20the%20videogame%20%22Dead%20Rising%202%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Chuck%20Greene",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nick%20Ramos",
"Frank%20West",
"Katie%20Greene"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20company%20made%20the%20Japanese%20RPG%20%22Dragon%20Quest%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Square%20Enix",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Capcom",
"Konami",
"Blizzard"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20type%20of%20genre%20is%20the%20controversial%202015%20game%20%22Hatred%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shoot%20%27Em%20Up",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Point%20%26%20Click",
"MMORPG",
"Simulation"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Touhou%3A%20Embodiment%20of%20Scarlet%20Devil%2C%20what%20song%20plays%20during%20Flandre%20Scarlet%27s%20boss%20fight%3F",
"correct_answer": "U.N.%20Owen%20Was%20Her",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Septette%20for%20the%20Dead%20Princess",
"Flowering%20Night",
"Pierrot%20of%20the%20Star-Spangled%20Banner"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20normal%20endings%20are%20there%20in%20Cry%20Of%20Fear%27s%20campaign%20mode%3F",
"correct_answer": "4",
"incorrect_answers": [
"5",
"3",
"6"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20the%20name%20of%20a%20team%20leader%20in%20Pok%C3%A9mon%20GO%3F",
"correct_answer": "Leif",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Blanche",
"Spark",
"Candela"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20which%20game%20does%20a%20character%20say%2C%20%22Sometimes%2C%20I%20dream%20about%20cheese%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Half%20Life%202",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Team%20Fortress%202",
"Dark%20Souls",
"Serious%20Sam%3A%20The%20Second%20Encounter"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20which%20feature%20was%20removed%20due%20to%20performance%20issues%20in%202016%3F",
"correct_answer": "Terraforming",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Building",
"Crafting",
"Multiplayer"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20Half-Life%20franchise%2C%20what%20is%20the%20real%20name%20of%20the%20%22gravity%20gun%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Zero-Point%20Energy%20Field%20Manipulator",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Universal%20Gravity%20Manipulation%20Device",
"Isaac%20Newton%27s%20Theory%20Disprover",
"Quantum%20Energy%20Displacement%20Modifier"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20video%20game%20%22League%20of%20Legends%22%20which%20character%20is%20known%20as%20%22The%20Sinister%20Blade%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Katarina",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Shaco",
"Akali",
"Zed"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20Overwatch%20character%20says%20the%20line%20%22Heroes%20never%20die%21%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mercy",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Reaper",
"Sonic",
"Ana"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Hitman%3A%20Blood%20Money%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20target%20in%20the%20mission%20%22Death%20of%20a%20Showman%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Joseph%20Clarence",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Swing%20King",
"Maynard%20John",
"Manuel%20Delgado"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20first%20primary%20weapon%20the%20player%20gets%20in%20%22PAYDAY%3A%20The%20Heist%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "AMCAR-4",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Brenner%2021",
"Reinbeck",
"M308"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20%22Fallout%204%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20dog%20you%20find%20at%20Red%20Rocket%20truck%20stop%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dogmeat",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sparky",
"Quazar",
"Chop"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20original%20name%20of%20%20%22Minecraft%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Cave%20Game",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Minecraft%3A%20Order%20of%20the%20Stone",
"Dig%20And%20Build",
"Infiniminer"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20regular%20Sunken%20Sea%20Scrolls%20are%20there%20in%20%22Splatoon%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "27",
"incorrect_answers": [
"32",
"30",
"5"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20weapon%20pack%20for%20%22PAYDAY%202%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Gage%20Weapon%20Pack%20%231",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Overkill%20Pack",
"The%20Gage%20Chivalry%20Pack",
"The%20Gage%20Historical%20Pack"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Dota%202%2C%20what%20is%20Earthshaker%27s%20real%20name%3F",
"correct_answer": "Raigor%20Stonehoof",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Banehallow%20Ambry",
"Carl",
"Barathrum"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20game%20%22Brawlhalla%22%2C%20what%20species%20is%20the%20character%20B%C3%B6dvar%20is%3F",
"correct_answer": "Half%20Human%20%2F%20Half%20Bear",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20Human",
"Half%20Wolf%20%2F%20Half%20Bear",
"Half%20Tiger%20%2F%20%20Half%20Human"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "When%20was%20Club%20Penguin%20launched%3F",
"correct_answer": "October%2024%2C%202005",
"incorrect_answers": [
"October%2021%2C%202005",
"March%2029%2C%202006",
"November%2022%2C%202004"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",
"correct_answer": "Vanilla",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Peach",
"Strawberry",
"Mint"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20creature%20that%20the%20main%20character%20befriends%20in%20%22The%20Last%20Guardian%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Trico",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nico",
"Wolf",
"Andazi"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20voices%20the%20character%20%22Vernon%20Cherry%22%20in%20%22Red%20Dead%20Redemption%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Casey%20Mongillo",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Tara%20Strong",
"Troy%20Baker",
"Rob%20Wiethoff"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20perk%20that%20was%20introduced%20in%20the%20%22Call%20Of%20Duty%3A%20Zombies%22%20map%2C%20%22Mob%20Of%20The%20Dead%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Electric%20Cherry",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Quick%20Revive",
"Vulture%20Aid",
"Tombstone"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20name%20of%20a%20city%20in%20the%20main%20island%20of%20PLAYERUNKNOWN%27S%20BATTLEGROUNDS%3F",
"correct_answer": "Belushya%20Guba",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Yasnaya%20Polyana",
"Pochinki",
"Georgopol"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20protagonist%27s%20first%20Persona%20in%20%22Persona%205%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Arsene",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mara",
"Izanagi",
"Sandaphlon"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20%22Resident%20Evil%202%22%2C%20what%20is%20Leon%20Kennedy%27s%20middle%20name%3F",
"correct_answer": "Scott",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Shaun",
"Simon",
"Sam"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20Crypt%20of%20the%20NecroDancer%20%282015%29%20character%20has%20a%20soundtrack%20by%20Jake%20%22Virt%22%20Kaufman%3F",
"correct_answer": "Uncle%20Eli",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cadence",
"Nocturna",
"Octavian%20%28Bard%29"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%20%22Portal%22%20series%2C%20who%20was%20Cave%20Johnson%27s%20personal%20assistant%3F",
"correct_answer": "Caroline",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Heather",
"Melissa",
"Jane"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20subtitle%20for%20Gran%20Turismo%203%3F",
"correct_answer": "A-Spec",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Championship",
"Drive",
"Nitro"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20main%20villain%20of%20the%20Crash%20Bandicoot%20series%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dr.%20Neo%20Cortex",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Dr.%20Evo-Cortex",
"Dr.%20Cortox",
"Sir%20Cartex"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Mario%20Kart%208%20Deluxe%20items%20will%20NOT%20make%20you%20invincible%3F",
"correct_answer": "Golden%20Mushroom",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Star",
"Bullet%20Bill",
"Boo"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20%22Kingdom%20Hearts%22%2C%20who%20abducts%20Jasmine%20in%20the%20Lamp%20Chamber%3F",
"correct_answer": "Riku",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Riku%20Replica",
"Xaldin",
"Captain%20Hook"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20genre%20is%20the%20Touhou%20Project%20associated%20with%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shoot%20%27em%20up%20%28bullet-hell%29%20%26%20Fighting",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Turn-Based%20Strategy",
"MMORPG",
"Building%20"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Sid%20Meier%27s%20Civilization%20V%2C%20which%20World%20Wonder%20can%20only%20be%20built%20in%20cities%20on%20or%20next%20to%20a%20desert%3F",
"correct_answer": "Petra",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Pyramids",
"Alhambra",
"Mausoleum%20of%20Maussollos"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20country%20is%20featured%20in%20Ace%20Combat%205%3A%20The%20Unsung%20War%3F",
"correct_answer": "Osea",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Aurelia",
"Australia",
"Japan"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20AK-47%27s%20name%20in%20Counter%20Strike%3A%20Source%3F",
"correct_answer": "CV-47",
"incorrect_answers": [
"AK-74",
"AK",
"CZ-75"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20which%20U.S.%20state%20is%20Far%20Cry%205%27s%20fictional%20setting%20%27Hope%20County%27%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Montana",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Idaho",
"Wyoming",
"North%20Carolina"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Splatoon%2C%20what%20is%20the%20age%20that%20inklings%20can%20freely%20change%20between%20squid%20and%20humanoid%20forms%3F",
"correct_answer": "14",
"incorrect_answers": [
"13",
"16",
"10"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20character%20you%20play%20as%20in%20Yume%20Nikki%3F",
"correct_answer": "Madotsuki",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Masada",
"Uboa",
"Poniko"
]
}
]